

UX UI DESIGNER

HIRING TEAM

ALGAECAL

22 E 5TH AVENUE #300

VANCOUVER, BC V5R 1G8

info@designeed.ca www.designeed.ca Linkedin.com/in/designeed in

To The Hiring Team,

I am excited to see the opening for the UX/UI Designer position on LinkedIn. You will find that I fit AlgaeCal's core values perfectly. Because I *care*, I create intuitive designs for clients to easily navigate and access information critical to their needs; in the pursuit of *excellence*, I read and engage in conversations that stretch my comfort zone; the *real* deal: I strive to make a difference in my design, this is why they are informed by data and feedback; always putting others ahead of myself, my active listening and "all-hands-on-deck" approach translates my clients'/*team*'s needs into impactful designs and results. With a formal background in UX/UI Design, paired with my education in health studies, I think I am uniquely positioned to be a great addition to the team of tops at AlgaeCal and would be delighted if you would consider my candidacy.

In my most recent project with "My Ultimate Acupuncture" (MUA), having interviewed my client for desired business outcomes and presented my recommendations, I have designed and coded MUA's revamped website. In conjunction with other services offered to the client, the result was a significant increase to the following month-over-month stats: +97% increase in unique visits, +128% increase in page views, and +87% increase in user engagement and time spent on the website.

The toughest challenge in my life would be my struggle with housing insecurity at the end of my high school career and into my twenties. I was faced with a decision to choose between survival. This challenge had taught me to be resilient and I held several jobs to maintain a roof over my head.

The last 3 books I read were: Never Split the Difference by Chris Voss, The Design of Everyday Things by Don Norman, and Company of One by Paul Jarvis. All three books were read for the purpose of adding value to clients/the business

For fun, I like to cook and see the joy my cooking brings to others. I am often amused by my husband when he is bewildered by my recreations of foods we've only eaten once in restaurants.

I am currently working as an outbound sales associate and working on freelance and volunteer UX/UI projects. I am looking to transition into a permanent UX/UI role.

You will find the link to my portfolio at the top right corner and my resume below. Thank you for your consideration.

YOURS SINCERELY,

Christine Su



Christine Su

UX UI DESIGNER

Profile

Certified UX Product Designer and user advocate with a keen eye for product usability and consumer behaviour in pursuit of increasing conversion rate and product confidence. Trained with market-ready UX skills to collaborate in solving usability problems and create seamless experiences for users. Through root-cause analysis, able to empathize with user pain points and provide adaptive solutions to meet both user and organizational needs.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

Freelance Product Designer

DESIGNEED | 2020 - Current

- + Led the end-to-end project for clients' websites including: copywriting, page layout, navigation flow of website, facilitation of client meetings to discuss the benefits of having an ecommerce website retail shop especially during pandemic lockdowns, implementation of ecommerce capabilities, appointment booking-ready websites, effective use of design thinking process, research, wireframe and prototype on Figma, brand consistency, UI elements to interact with users, and Responsive Web Design.
- + Worked closely with Kingdom Dev's Project Manager to determine business requirements and, in collaboration with an international project team, successfully delivered on design work under tight timelines.
- + Created a user journey map leveraging User Centric Design principles and Design Thinking that produced positive user experience after productlaunch. Shipfusion and Shopify's initial launch in November attracted 20 registrations, which has since doubled.
- + Pioneered design system and ensured on-brand consistency.
- + Produced user flow, wireframe, Hi-Fi Mockup, and working prototypes.
- + Developed user experience solutions across multiple devices (mobile, table, laptop, desktop).
- + Influenced client to adopt user advocacy in UX design concepts in order to provide a clear call-to-action to users on the website.
- + Designed and printed marketing material stationeries including business cards, appointment cards, brochures, and gift certificates.

DESIGNEED Clients

- My Ulimate Acupuncture & TCM Clinic
- XL Tea
- · Serenity Gifts
- · Shipfusion and Shopify
- Kingdom Dev Welcome Church Project and CANHK Project

OTHER EXPERIENCE

Outbound Sales Customer Service Nordia | 2021 - Current

Dietary Aide Sunnybrook Hospital | 2017 - 2019

647.395.6893 info@designeed.ca www.designeed.ca ●

in

SKILLS

Linkedin.com/in/designeed

User Experience (UX) User Interface (UI) Figma (Software) Competitor Analysis Adobe (Software) Web Development Wireframe Project Management Mockup Typography Page Layout Storyboarding Flowcharts Colour Theory Storyboarding HTML Presentations Branding JavaScript

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATE

Bachelor

Bachelor of Science, Kinesiology Honours York University 2015-2021

UX UI FRONT-END DEV

University of Toronto 2020